All right, you guys, my guy just
pulled up on a yacht right here.
We're going to go and figure out what he was able
to do to afford this and see if this is his boat.
Let's see what he has to say.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you, man.
Is this your yacht?
Yeah.
And what do you do for a living out
in Miami to be able to afford a yacht, man?
Seriously, what do you do for a living?
Well, I run a health care company.
A health care company?
Yeah.
How long have you been a business owner for?
Four years.
Over the last four years, what's the most amount
of money that you've ever made in a single year?
About $25 million.
$30 million.
And then we did around $19 million in profit.
$10 million.
Now, we go all over the country just asking
people how they became successful for the younger generation.
Is it cool if we ask
you a few questions for the channel?
Just ask.
You want an interview?
Absolutely, man.
Come on board.
Appreciate you, man.
All right.
Let's go.
Miami, Florida is home to nearly 40,000 millionaires.
And if you've ever been to Miami, you know that
there's always some multimillion dollar yachts right out on the water.
But what exactly do these people do?
Well, today, we're going to find out just that.
And I'm going to be going all over the
wealthiest parts of Miami to ask multimillionaires and yacht owners
what they did to be able to afford these boats
and how you can start your path to becoming fine.
And to be free in 2024.
So with that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
All right, you guys.
We just got to our first
marina out here in Miami, Florida.
There's a couple people out on their yachts right now.
I'm going to go up and see if
we can talk to these people, get some game,
what they were able to do to be
able to afford these yachts out here in Miami.
Excuse me, sir.
Quick question for you, man.
Is this your yacht?
Yeah, it is.
And what do you do for living out in Miami?
To be able to afford a yacht, man?
I'm actually in e-commerce.
How long have you been a business owner for?
I've been in e-commerce for about four years now.
Four years.
And over these last four years, what's the most amount
of money that you've ever made in a single year?
Last year, we did $30 million.
$30 million.
$32 million, yeah.
And then we did around $19 million in profit.
How old are you now?
I'm 22.
You're 22 years old.
Yeah.
And how old were you when you became a millionaire?
Let me tell you something first, all right?
Do you want me to go deep?
Yeah, go deep.
Okay.
So when I was five years old, I witnessed my
mom get, you know, she died in front of my eyes.
At 16 years old, my best
friend got shot in the head.
At 17 years old, I got kicked out of college.
At 19 years old, I was a millionaire.
So embracing the struggle, realizing that the struggle is what makes you you,
is what's going to help you get to where you want to be.
And realizing that the struggle is just preparing you for the person
that you need to be to steward that is going to help you.
And realizing that, you know,
God does everything for a reason.
Like, you might not understand it now.
Your whole situation might be
completely fucked up right now.
But if you just see that bigger picture and you're
able to work towards it, don't just sit there and pray.
But work towards it and work on those principles.
You're going to get there.
It's only a matter of time.
But you have to focus on your own race.
How can somebody go from seven to eight figures?
The biggest thing with going from seven to eight figures is trying to get out of
that kind of like solopreneur mindset and thinking that you can do it all by yourself.
Making a million dollars, you can do it by yourself.
It's not that hard.
You know, it might take
you a little bit of time.
But going from seven to eight figures, you
need to start delegating and relieving your time.
Because as an entrepreneur, you have to
realize that your biggest asset is your time.
And the most important thing for you to do is
create ideas and then delegate those ideas to the worker.
Because that's what the school system
was built for, for the workers.
Do you know the story about free thinkers
and workers and why the school system was created?
Well, I think it's kind of
how to do like the Rockefellers.
Exactly.
John D. Rockefeller created the education board in 1903.
And he said that he wanted
a nation of workers, not free thinkers.
So who are the workers?
Who are the free thinkers?
The workers are the people
who work for the free thinkers.
People who come up with their own ideas and
then delegate them for a fraction of the money.
And then they go and do the work for
the free thinkers and make them the big money.
So once you get from that seven figure
mark, you're trying to get to eight figures.
Find people who are smarter than you.
You know, I just.
Dropped out of college.
You know, I'm not the smartest in the group, but
I have people who work for me who went to Yale.
I have a person who worked
for me who went to Stanford.
My CFO went to Harvard.
So it's about being able to pay people what they're valued
at so that you can get what you want in return.
What keeps people broke in today's world?
Mindset.
It's 80% mindset and 20% skill set.
Once you get the mindset, now
it's time to apply the skill set.
But you can't start thinking about making money until you are in
the mind to learn how to steward that money and multiply that money.
Otherwise, you're never going to be able to get more.
Majority of people, if I gave
you a million dollars right now,
you would be broken six months.
Not because you're stupid is because you don't have the mindset to steward that
money and you don't know what to do with it when you get it.
But if you have the skill set and you have the mindset,
then you're bound to turn that into 10 million in six months.
That was phenomenal.
Absolutely.
Oh man.
All right, you guys.
So the first interview of the day just went crazy.
My guy made over 30 million dollars since last year.
But what did he say was the number
one thing that's keeping people broke in today's world?
It's their mindset.
He said it was 80% mindset
and 20% skill set for him.
And that's how he was able to
become a millionaire at 19 years old.
This video just got off the air.
It got off to a crazy start,
but we got tons more to come.
So let's go get this next one.
Come on.
All right, you guys.
We're at our next marina right now, man.
And as you can see, this video is super
hard to make because of how private it is, man.
Super high net worth individuals, man.
It's not easy to get access
to these people to own these boats.
But ultimately, all you can do is keep trying.
We're going to find a way in.
There's no way that we're leaving this video
without getting on one of these yachts, man.
So let's see what they have to say.
This guy's coming out right here.
My guy's coming to the gate right now.
So I'm going to try to get in here.
Yes, sir.
I got a question for you.
What's that?
I grew it to over 3 million
followers, and I go all over the country.
I'm based in Austin.
Just ask me.
You want an interview.
Just a few questions.
Is that cool?
So you don't even know
who I am yet, do you?
Not yet, sir.
I'd love to find out, though.
I'm going to find out, though.
I'm going to be the most
famous guy you'll ever meet here.
I believe it.
Oh, I know.
It's true.
Could we do it over here?
Is that cool?
Over by the boat?
Yeah, come on.
Let's go.
Awesome, man.
I appreciate that.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
I've been in every industry.
And I've done everything.
Everything.
I ended up owning a large strip
club, the largest strip club in Connecticut.
I'm also a certified gemologist, precious gems.
I had high-end jewelry stores.
I also had a gambling ship
on the west coast of Florida.
I owned a major motion picture movie
studio, the biggest east of the Mississippi River.
How could somebody get a yacht in today's world?
Buy one.
Buy what?
How old are you now?
Oh, let me see.
How old am I now?
The sun is going around
the earth 72 times, I guess?
Yeah.
Everybody calls me up and says, Rick,
how the fuck are you still alive?
And my answer is, I don't have a fucking clue.
Right.
Yeah.
If you were to go back in time and have a conversation with your
20-year-old self, what's the best advice that you would give to your younger self?
So, I'll tell you this.
Steven Jobs said it beautifully,
and I love what he said.
And what he said was this.
You could have a Timex watch.
You could have a Rolex watch.
They will both tell you the right time.
And then he also said, you can get somewhere in your Rolls Royce
or you can get somewhere in your little Volkswagen, which maybe costs $1,000.
But they will both stay.
They will both stay.
And they will both still get you there.
And that, to me, is the
smartest thing anybody could ever say.
So, it's not a question of money.
It's a question of the way you are, the way you
treat life, the way you treat yourself, the way you treat others.
And me, personally, I love everybody.
And everybody knows that.
What's your best self-improvement
advice to somebody out there?
The best thing I could
tell anybody is, you know what?
When you hit bottom, the
only way to go is up.
Okay?
So, you can hit bottom, but then from there,
you go up and start going to the top.
And have you ever been broke before?
Of course.
And what did God like for you?
Like, how did you know that you wanted to
become serious about really becoming successful and finding that success?
You know something?
There's an old saying.
I think it was done by Caesar or somebody.
It says, know thyself.
You got to know yourself.
You got to know what's good
for you, what's not good for you.
Use your brain.
Use the brain that God gave you.
All right, you guys.
So, we were waiting over on
the other side of the gate.
My guy, Rick Sauce, he came over, let us in,
and just did a great interview outside of the boat, man.
Some of my favorite life advice that
I've ever heard was just dropping that interview.
But he brought up how Steve Jobs said, it doesn't
matter if you have a Timex or a Rolex on.
It still tells the same time regardless.
Or if you're driving in a Volkswagen or Rolls Royce,
they both get you from point A to point B.
Don't get caught up stressing about what
other people have, what you don't have.
Man, those people put in more blood,
sweat, and tears than 99% of other people.
So, just remember that you're on your own journey.
And if you want great things, it takes sacrifice, man.
But we're all going to make this happen.
Let's go get this next interview.
Excuse me, guys.
Question for you, man.
Would love to ask you guys just a couple
quick questions on some advice to the younger generation.
Is that cool?
Let me see your Instagram.
I got you, brother.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
Basically, I was in the car.
I love entertainment.
What was the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
About $25 million.
$25 million.
How long have you been a business owner for?
Business owner since the age of 18.
How old are you now?
You're 56 years old.
Actually.
What's the secret to looking so young at 56?
Yeah, I'm not going to say olive oil.
Just a good life and to keep it simple.
Let me ask you this.
If you were to go back to when
you started your first business, what's the number one
thing that you wish you would have known?
Go to school.
Education.
Yeah.
Get a better education.
If I had a better education, it would
be a lot further along, a lot younger.
best advice I can give you. So you say that
a college degree is kind of necessary to be successful?
College degree is definitely not necessary to be
successful, but it gives you the tools to
make better decisions. Right. And I guess
among yourself and the most highly successful people
that you study and know, what is that one trait
that they all have in common? Risk. Take the risk.
Can't take the risk, you're not going to get
the reward. That's what it comes down to. Take the
risk or lose the chance. Exactly. What was
the biggest risk that you took throughout your career?
Everything I've done. Make a leap.
Believe in yourself. Take that chance.
Have you ever been broke before? Oh, absolutely. Yeah. 100%.
And how old were you
when you became a millionaire? 24.
How did you find that self-belief though to
be able to do all these amazing things,
right? Because a lot of people don't
doubt themselves. That is one denominator we just
can't teach. You have to believe in yourself.
And if you don't have that belief, because we
need people that don't believe either. We need
those guys who are going to turn and
crank the shafts and turn those
wheels. So we can't all be winners.
So we had just pulled up on our next shot and
my guy, Franco, was so nice to do the interview with
us. But my number one
takeaway from that interview was that
the biggest thing that enabled him to make $25
million in a single year and become a millionaire
in his early twenties wasn't a particular skill
that he learned. It wasn't a person that came
and gave him the money, but rather it
was the self-belief that he found in himself.
See the most successful people, man,
they have this unwavering belief that they're
going to achieve that success. And you can't
teach that or give that to anybody else, man.
So shout out to that man, Franco,
man. Let's go get this next one.
All right, you guys, my guy just pulled up on
a yacht right here. We're going to go and figure
out what he was able to do to afford this and see
if this is his boat. Let's see what he has to say.
Excuse me, sir. Question for
you, man. Is this your yacht?
Yeah.
And what do you do for a living out in
Miami to be able to afford a yacht, man? Seriously,
what do you do for a living?
Well, I run a healthcare company.
A healthcare company. How long have
you been a business owner for?
Four years.
Over the last four years, what's the most amount
of money that you've ever made in a single year?
$10 million.
$10 million. Now we go all over the
country just asking people how they became successful
for the younger generation. Is it cool if
we ask you a few questions for the channel?
Absolutely, man. Come on board.
Let's run it. Can we run it? Cool.
All right, let's go.
So you're ready to do this? Let
me show you the boat around first.
Is that cool?
Yeah.
All right, man, let's do it.
All right.
Among yourself and the most highly
successful people that you study and know,
what is that one trait
that they all have in common?
I will tell you one thing, man. One
thing these people all have in common. Sometimes, man,
they're not that bright. I don't know.
They're crazy and so forth, but they're all
high.
Hungry as hell. It's insane. It's like they're
crazy to a point. They're all super, super,
super hungry. It's like, I'm going to do it, and
I'm going to do this, and I'm going to do that,
and they execute. It's not no BS. They'll execute
on their craziness. So I'd say hunger. Hunger and
actually executing on it, but hunger the first
thing. These guys don't stop scheming and thinking
of how they're going to get to
the next level and all. It's insane.
Have you ever been broke before?
Jesus, yes. Yes, yes. Yes. People having to donate
food to my family. For a couple of weeks,
yeah.
I know what that's like.
What was the number one book that changed your
life or number one book that changed your business
that you think everybody should
read your number one book recommendation?
Dude, I don't want to be cliche. What I'm
going to say here, people are going to be like,
eh, but if you really, really, really go into
it, as an entrepreneur, you're going to be really
surprised, especially to certain sections of this book.
Some of you already know what I'm going to
say. It's the Bible, bro. It's the Bible.
The amount of entrepreneurs in that Bible is insane.
Don't go read the Spirit. I'm talking about just,
even if you don't believe in God or whatever,
just go read on the
entrepreneurship lessons, man. It's insane.
There's nothing to me, and I reflect on that.
I always reflect on that. Then, yeah, you've got
other books that will, I think, complement
even the Bible, like Think and Grow Rich.
Absolutely, but I start and end always with the Bible.
How important has that faith been
to the success of your business?
Oh, that's everything. That's everything. This
wouldn't have happened without that. This wouldn't
have happened without my faith, without the woman that
I'm with, which is my wife, for almost a
decade. That's a whole different conversation.
Those are the pillars, the spiritual pillars
that have held up the person of who I am.
The going gets rough. It's like, whoa, it's rocky. Who's
here with me, and what do I hang on to?
Yeah, it's my faith. It's my marriage. I have
friends that have been with me for years that
I can always hang on to. Your circle
of spiritual components has to be strong. Absolutely.
Last thing I want you to tell them, and I want
you to look at them, and you've got to tell them
the importance of believing in yourself and your
dream. You never gave up. You had that vision.
You had that dream, and you
believed in it all along. Tell them.
Listen, if you're in doubt, man, and I wish I could
just reach out to you, grab you by the face right now.
If you're in doubt, do it.
Do not doubt, bro. Do not doubt, okay? You can do
it. You can do it. There's a God that loves you,
and if you have those goals and dreams in your
life, you will get it. Listen, you have to build
the confidence. For you to build the confidence, you got
to hit the goals. For you to hit the goals,
you have to design the timeline and the process
to do it, okay? And it's daily steps, daily promises
to yourself. Don't break promises to yourself,
or else you're breaking promises with the world
around you and with the goals that you've
set up. You want to hit those goals? Discipline
yourself to hit those daily goals to ultimately
hit your big goal, and all of a sudden,
all of a sudden, you'll walk into a room
and people will be like, wow, that person's full
of confidence. Wow, that person, look at their
watch. Look at what they got. No, because daily,
they hit the promises that they promised
themselves, and then they hit those goals
they put at the end of their timeline. Go
get it. Hey, they don't teach that shit in school,
you guys. That was phenomenal. All right, you guys,
my guy, Dr. D, made $10 million this last
year, and he's one of the most
successful healthcare entrepreneurs in the entire world,
and he was nice enough to not only let us come
on his yacht, but he just took us all around Miami,
giving some insights for the younger generation out there.
I have a very special announcement to make
for you guys. We just launched the Hard Knocks
newsletter, where we're going to be sending
out weekly updates, insights, and lessons from some
of the most successful entrepreneurs in the entire world.
You won't want to miss it, so subscribe now.
The link is in the description, but with
that being said, like and subscribe for amazing content
on the way, and click here to watch
our full video going all over Dallas, asking multi-millionaires
how they became wealthy and how you can
start your path to becoming financially free in 2024.